COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
You have to think when using Jutsu.
They can be used against you.
Also, don't get caught
in an obvious trap, you fool.
A Ninja must see
through deception... got it?
I know that!
You know, you say that because
you don't get it. Listen up.
Your movements are wasteful.
Now!
He finally dropped his guard!
You're so...
No way!
You jerk, Sasuke! You overdid it.
Damn! Another substitution...?
He must have found out my location
with those Shuriken!
He purposely lowered his guard!
Serves me right...
I fell for the trap.
So he's over there, eh...
Sasuke-kun... Where are you...?!
Don't tell me,
Kakashi-sensei already...
No!
That couldn't happen to Sasuke-kun, right?!
Safe! He didn't notice me.
Sakura, behind you.
Huh?!
What's up with that "A Ninja must see
through deception" stuff?!
Damn it! I'll never fall for his trap again!
I fell for it again!
Fail?
Kakashi's conclusion
What was that?! Huh?!
Hold on! Where's Sensei?!
Huh?! What's going on?!
Huh?! What's what?!
Sakura...
Sasuke-kun?!
Sa... Saku... Ra...
P-Please... help... me...
Maybe I went a bit overboard...
But it's really something
she should notice...
Was that voice... Sakura's...?
Shinobi Battle Skill #2, Genjutsu.
Sakura was easily lured.
Genjutsu, huh...?
An illusory mind-controlling technique.
I'm not surprised she got lured.
However...
I'm different from them.
Why don't you say that after
you get a bell... Sasuke-kun?
It's no use just using
straightforward attacks.
A trap?!
What?!
This guy's...?!
What a guy.
There's no time
to read "Make-Out Paradise."
What...?
I...?!
That's right! I saw Sasuke-kun on
the verge of dying and I...
Sasuke-kun!
Don't die and leave me here!!
Where are you?!
So that's what it looks like
behind the logs.
Oh! There are box lunches on the stone!
A Ninja must see through deception... eh?
Well! I'll acknowledge that
you're different from those two.
Horse!
Tiger!
Fire Style! Fireball Jutsu!
What?! That's not a Jutsu
that a Genin can do...
He shouldn't have
enough Chakra yet!
He's gone!
Is he behind me?! No, above me?!
Where is he?!
I'm under you!!
Wha...?!
Earth Style: Headhunter Jutsu.
Shinobi Battle Skill #3, Ninjutsu.
How's that? You can't move, heh?
Although, you're... already starting
to make your mark.
But, oh well.
They do say that the nail that sticks up
gets hammered down, so...
Damn it!
I don't have to naively take those bells.
I'll just eat in secret right now!
Let's eat!!
Hey.
I was just joking...
Too late!
Damn it...! Is there this much of
a difference in strength...?
Sakura...
This time it's a freshly severed head?!
What's up with her?
Sasuke-kun?
You're okay!
Hey, cut it out!
Don't cling to me!
There's not much time left until noon.
I'm going.
Sasuke-kun, you're still going
after the bells?!
I was able to touch them last time.
Next time I'll be able to take them.
What?!
I-I see.
Sure enough,
you're awesome, Sasuke-kun.
There's no way I can take
the bells from Sensei.
At this rate, I'll face
separation from Sasuke-kun...
Uh... say. There's really no time left...
So let's just take it easy and
try again next time.
I'm the only one
who can kill that man.
Huh...? What?
You mean Sensei?
At that time... I was crying.
Crying...?
My...
What...? What is it...?
I'm an avenger. I must become stronger
than that man...
I don't have time for setbacks here...
... to kill a certain man!
Damn it... I wasted my time talking.
Sasuke-kun...
Oh-oh, your stomachs are growling...
By the way, about this exercise...
Well! There's no need for you guys
to go back to the Academy.
What? I... All I did was lay unconscious.
Is that okay?
Love is victorious!! Shannaro!!
Yahoo!
Then, then!
That means the three of us...
Yes. The three of you...
must quit being Ninja!!
N-No way!
Kakashi hasn't passed
a single person this whole time...
Iruka...
Even I don't know if it's good for
those kids to become Shinobi right away...
However...
Kakashi's judgments were correct...
Quit being Ninja?! What do you mean?!
Uh, well it's true, we weren't able to
take the bells.
But why do we have to be told to "quit"?!
That's because you're all squirts who
don't have the qualifications to become Ninja.
Oh!
Sasuke-kun!
I'm saying you're squirts.
Don't step on Sasuke-kun!!
Are you kids thinking that
being a Ninja is easy? Huh?
Why do you think you're doing
this exercise in teams?
Huh?! What do you mean?
Put simply...
it's as if you guys have no
understanding of the answer to this test.
Answer...?
Yes. The answer that determines
passing or failing of this test.
That's... what I've wanted to ask
about for a while now.
Man, are you guys brainless or what?
Don't you get the meaning of
the three-man team?!
Jeez!! What of three people to a team?!
That's... teamwork!
You mean, working together?
Exactly. But it's too late even
if you realize that now.
You might've been able to...
take the bells if the three of you
had come at me...
Well, it's too bad.
Now wait a minute.
Why use teamwork if
there were only two bells?
If the three of us were to desperately go
take the bells with one having to hold back,
that wouldn't be teamwork.
That'd create internal discord.
Of course!
This is a test set up to purposely
place you against each other.
It's under just such conditions
where one's own interests aren't the issue.
The intention was to select those
who could prioritize teamwork...
Despite this, you fools...
Sakura!
You were only concerned with Sasuke and
you didn't even know where he was.
And you didn't care for Naruto who was
right in front of your eyes...
Naruto!
All you do is run solo...
You labeled the other two as hindrances
and acted on your own...
Missions are carried out in teams!
There's no mistaking that Ninja need
unsurpassed individual skills...
But "teamwork" is considered
more important than that.
Individual actions that disrupt teamwork
throw the team into crisis and lead to death...
For example...
"Sakura! Kill Naruto, or else Sasuke dies..."
What?! What?! What?!
Is what will... happen.
Oh, I was so surprised.
On top of having a hostage taken,
you're faced with two impossible choices
and end up being killed.
Every mission is
a life-risking assignment.
Look at this...
The many names engraved
on this stone...
These are all Ninja who are called
heroes in the village.
That, that, that, that! I like that!
I've decided now to get
my name engraved there, too!
A hero! A hero!
I'm not going to die like a dog!
But... they're not just ordinary heroes.
No kidding. Then, what kind
of heroes are they?
Hey! Hey!
They are heroes
who were killed in action.
Killed in action?
It means they died
performing a mission.
This is a memorial.
The names of my friends
are also engraved here...
I'll give you guys one more chance!
However, after noon it'll be
a harsher battle to take the bell.
Those who want to take on
the challenge can eat lunch.
However, don't let Naruto have any.
It's punishment for breaking the rules and
attempting to eat lunch on your own.
If someone lets him eat...
that person will be disqualified
on the spot.
I make the rules, here. Got it?!
I must be going.
Listen to me, Iruka.
What?
No matter what the result,
don't hold it against Kakashi...
Alright.
I'm okay with not eating lunch!
No sweat at all!
No sweat...
Here.
H-Hey, Sasuke-kun.
Sensei just said...!
It's okay.
There's no sign of him now.
The three of us are going to go
take the bells together.
It'll be trouble for me
if he becomes a hindrance, so...
Sasuke-kun...
Sakura-chan...
Thanks...
Don't thank me.
Just hurry up and eat.
But...
I'm on... a diet...
I mean I just eat less than Sasuke-kun.
So you don't need to worry.
But...
See...
Wha...?!
Hurry it up.
We don't know when he'll be back...
It's just this one time.
Okay? You got it?!
I got it.
You three!
Yikes!
You defied the rules so that
means you know what's coming...
Do you have... something to say?
But you see...
What?!
But! But! But!
You said, Sensei!
These guys...
We're a three-man team, right?
That's right!
The three of us are one, so...!
That's right! That's right!
That's right!
The three of you are one, eh...
You pass!
What?!
We passed?! Why?!
You guys are the first.
Up until now, it was always just dunces
who would meekly listen to what I said.
A Ninja must see through deception...
In the world of Ninja,
those who break rules and codes
are branded as garbage...
But...
Those who don't cherish their friends are
garbage worse than that.
He's... He's... kinda... cool...
That's it for the exercise...
Everyone passes!
Team 7 starts their mission
tomorrow!
Yes, sir!
I did it!! I'm a Ninja!
Ninja! Ninja!
Let's go home.
Shannaro!
I...
knew this is how it'd turn out!
Untie the rope!
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
Oh, please! It'd been nothing but
blah missions until now.
And just when I thought I'd finally
gotten an awesome mission,
to think it'd be body guarding
this old man.
He mocks the hell out of me,
calling me a brat.
I'll tell him a thing or two.
Someday I'll be...
Hey, are you listening?!
Next episode:
"Important Mission! Heading to the Country of the Wave!"
Don't miss me kick butt!